(Leonard:)Think it's gonna rain?
(Leonard:)Instead of underpants, I covered
my crotch with potato salad. Thoughts?
(Leonard:)I know what'll cheer you up.
Let's play one of your driving games.
(Sheldon:)All right. This game is called Traitors.
(Sheldon:)I will name three historical figures...
(Sheldon:)...put them in order
of the heinousness of their betrayal:
(Sheldon:)Benedict Arnold, Judas,
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
(Leonard:)You really think I belong
with Benedict Arnold and Judas?
(Sheldon:)You're right. Judas had the decency
to hang himself after what he did.
(Leonard:)Can't you at least try to understand
how much this means to me?
Round two: Leonard Hofstadter,
Darth Vader, Rupert Murdoch.
(Leonard:)Rupert Murdoch?
(Sheldon:)He owns Fox
and they cancelled Firefly.